expats love Singapore for many things
superior health care is one but it does
get more expensive every year which is
why a corporate medical plan may not be
enough and sometimes it doesn't cover
everyone at home what if all of you can
be protected in Singapore and overseas
FWD international health insurance gives
you a comprehensive plan that stays with
you wherever you go
benefits include cashless outpatient
treatment from FW DS global network of
clinics and comprehensive
hospitalization coverage there's more
when you stay healthy and keep out of
the hospital you'll see your coverage
double under our plan getting FWD
international health insurance is easy
do it yourself online pick the add-ons
that you need and within minutes you'll
be covered by your personalized plan
enjoy greater value when you buy as a
family get your quote online now if you
have questions we're here to help
[Music]